Deepchand's recommendation for today is
Ultratech Cement,
Reliance, Bajaj Finance, Bajaj Financier
[music].
And the most important purchases, if you ca
n't afford anything else, you can buy Shree Cement. You can buy
Petronet LNG.
You can buy Boss. Atul's price is very
good. I also have the
applique type Mahanagar Gas and Mesh.
Kotak Mahindra Bank. Friends, these are at a
very good and excellent price. You
can also include sports.
You can buy A Persistent System.
SBI Life can be included in your purchases.
Remember, whatever it is and whatever it is,
this market is amazing. This market belongs to the courageous, the bold, the courageous, the daring,
and
those who have Door Desi, Door Nagari Nagari near their hearts.
And those who know
how to improve themselves in the future,
this is their market. This is not the market of those
who want to tarnish it by name
and who say that it's like a casino.
This is not a place for gamblers. This is definitely
not a place for gamblers.